你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hellova you beautiful people.
所以在上一段视频中，我给你们留下了一个扣人心弦的问题，我们有一些亟待解决的问题
So in the last video I left you with kind of a cliffhanger with some burning questions that we have
关于APT包管理器是如何工作的。
about how apt package manager works.
首先，缓存是如何到达那里的。
How does the cache get there in the first place.
我们怎样才能确保现金是最新的。
How can we make sure that the cash is kept up to date.
好的，这些是我们将在这段视频中回答的问题，在这段视频结束时，您将会知道
Well these are the questions that we'll be answering in this video by the end of this video you'll know
如何更新您的现金。
how to update your cash.
您还知道如何使用这笔钱将系统上的所有软件升级到最新版本
And you also know how to use that cash to upgrade all of the software on your system to the most uptodate
只需一个简单的命令即可升级。
level with one simple command.
这将是非常棒的，我相信你是的，你会开始明白为什么包裹经理
And this is going to be so awesome and I'm sure that you are you'll begin to see why package managers
远远优于您可能习惯使用的简单向导。
are far superior to the simple wizards that you may be used to using.
现在我等不及要给你看这些东西了。
Now I can't wait to show you this stuff.
所以，让我们继续直截了当地谈吧。
So let's just go ahead and get right into it.
好的。
OK.
那么，缓存中的列表最初是如何真正到达那里的呢？
So how do the lists in the cache actually get there in the first place.
这些列表实际上是从互联网上某处的服务器下载的，这些服务器
Well these lists are actually downloaded from servers somewhere on the Internet and these servers are
由可信来源维护，并包含所有现有软件包的最新列表。
maintained by credible sources and contain up to date lists of all existing packages.
正如我们在上一段视频中提到的，为了让我们的现金正常工作，缓存中的文件
And as we mentioned in the last video in order for our cash to be functional the files in the cache
必须与服务器上的文件相同。
must be the same as the files on the server.
这对于软件存储库尤其重要。
This is especially important for the software repositories.
所以我和我一起思考Linux社区的另一个问题，那就是全世界有数以百万计的人
So I think with me about the Linux community for another there are millions of people around the world
所有人都在为这个庞大的软件主体做出贡献，并一直在创造东西。
all contributing to this massive body of software and creating things all the time.
这一庞大的群体同时为软件存储库和产品做出贡献，这些软件存储库和产品
This massive body of people contributing simultaneously to the software repositories and products that
软件变化很大，而且经常变化。
software changes a lot and it changes often.
错误得到修复，安全漏洞得到修补。
Bugs get fix security holes get patched.
将添加新功能。
New features get added.
文档已编成代码，依此类推。
Documentation is codified and so on and so forth.
现在，有时程序开发得太多，以至于它们需要新的依赖项才能工作。
Now sometimes programs get developed so much that they require new dependencies in order to work.
尽管进行了所有这些更改，但现在您的系统上的所有软件都会保留下来，并且可以管理所有东西
And in spite all of these changes keep in all the software on your system today and managing everything
手动操作只会是一场彻头彻尾的噩梦。
yourself manually would just be a complete nightmare.
它就是行不通。
It just wouldn't work.
有太多的空间让一个人犯错误，有太多的事情需要跟踪。
There's too much room for a person to make a mistake and too much stuff to keep track of.
但幸运的是，你不必这么做。
But fortunately you don't have to.
APT包管理器有一种使用缓存的方法来确保系统上的所有软件
The apt package manager has a way of using the cache to make sure that all the software on your system
完全是最新的。
is completely up to date.
这就是它的工作原理。
And here's how it works.
因此，您需要做的第一件事是更新您的现金，并为此运行sudo apt get update。
So the first thing you need to do is to update your cash and to do that you'd run sudo apt get update.
好的，这就是你要运行的命令。
OK and that's the command you'd run.
现在请注意，我们需要如何使用这里开头的sudo命令。
Now notice how we need to use the sudo command at the beginning here.
这是因为我们要对文件系统上的重要文件进行更改，并且需要管理员
Now that's because we're going to make changes to important files on our file system and we need administrator
特权才能做到这一点。
privileges in order to do so.
我们使用的是apt get，而不是apt缓存，因为我们将从存储库获取数据，因此
And instead of apt cache we're using apt get because we're going to get data from the repositories so
我们会得到最新的名单并更新，我们会更新名单和我们的现金，以确保
we'll be getting the updated lists and update we'll update the lists and our cash to make sure that
其中的包版本与存储库中的包版本相同。
the package versions in there are the same as the package versions in the repositories.
但当然，为了让这项技术发挥作用，我们需要连接到互联网。
But of course in order for this to work we need to be connected to the Internet.
所以我在录制这段视频之前重新标记了我们的互联网连接。
So I relabeled our internet connection before recording this video.
因此，如果您正在追随，请确保您也重新启用了您的。
So if you are following along make sure you re-enable yours too.
如果我们现在运行so sudo apt get update，它将要求我们输入密码，因为我们使用的是
And if we run now so sudo apt get update it will ask us to enter our password because we are using the
SUDO命令，或者我们输入该命令，然后按Enter键，您可以看到它获得了大量不同的
sudo commands or we enter that and we press enter and you can see that it's getting loads of different
来自Buntu存储库的列表，它已经下载并安装了它们。
lists from the buntu repositories and it's downloaded them and installing them.
现在它将更新我们的现金，这可能需要不同的时间，这取决于需要多长时间
Now it's going to be updating our cash which might take various amount of time depending on how long
自从你更新信息以来就是这样了。
it's been since you've updated.
但是我们的已经走了，现在已经完工了。
But ours is gone and completed now.
现在我们已经更新了缓存，它将拥有最新的包号和依赖关系
So now that we've updated the cache will have the most up to date package numbers and dependencies for
所有的包裹都是现金，这样我们就有了最新的缓存。
all the packages in cash so that we have an up to date cache.
如果我们电脑上的一些软件过时了怎么办？
What if some of the software on our computer is out of date.
我们如何将我们的软件升级到新版本的软件包列表中的最新版本。
How can we upgrade our software to the newest versions that are in the new versions of the package lists.
老实说，这真的很容易，而且相当神奇。
Well that's actually really easy and quite magical to be honest.
因此，要升级从存储库安装的系统上的每一个软件，
So to upgrade every single piece of software on your system that you install from the repository is
你所需要做的就是打字。
all you need to do is type.
我玩了屏幕速成游戏，很容易升级。
I play the screen sudo apt get upgrade.
好的，现在我们来看一下“代表”。
OK now this will run through so Representer.
这将运行所有软件包列表，并查看我们系统上的所有软件
This will run through all the package lists and see all the software that we've got on our system and
它会告诉我们哪些是过时的，哪些需要更新，还会告诉您需要多少
it will tell us what's out of date and what needs to be updated and it also tell you how much needs
将被安装等等，并且它要求批准才能继续。
to be installed and so on and it asks for approbation to continue.
如果我按“是”的话。
If I press yes.
因此，这将通过更新的缓存运行，并查看系统上的哪些包在后面
So this is going to run on through the updated cache and see what packages on your system are behind
并找出需要安装哪些新依赖项，以及不再需要哪些依赖项。
it and figure out what new dependencies need to be installed and which ones are no longer required.
他们会告诉您需要多少空间，诸如此类，然后再请求您的许可才能继续。
They'll tell you how much space is required and so and so before asking your permission to continue.
但现在我们已经给了它许可，它将继续并开始更新上的每一个软件
But now that we've given it permission it will go ahead and start updating every piece of software on
系统或下载所需的软件包，将其解包、安装并自动删除旧版本
the system or download the required packages unpack them install them and remove the old versions automatically
整个系统上使用存储库安装的每个单独的软件。
for every single piece of software on the entire system that was installed using the repositories.
这是一个功能非常强大的自动化系统，这就是使用包管理器的美妙之处。
This is an incredibly powerful automated system and this is really the beauty of using a package manager.
您不必像以前那样访问网站并手动下载每个新包
You don't have to go to the Web site and download manually each piece each new package like you might
必须在Windows或Mac上运行。
have to do on Windows or Mac.
我们必须下载新的安装程序，或者单击以获取每个不同软件的更新。
We've got to download the new installer or click for updates on each different piece of software.
现在，您需要做的就是升级通过存储库安装的所有内容
Now all you have to do is want to upgrade upgrade everything that was installed through the repositories
将升级到可帮助您提高安全性的最新版本级别。
will be upgraded to the newest version levels which helps you with security.
它帮助你拥有最现代的特征，而且绝对是。
It helps you with having the most modern features and it's just absolutely.
另外，如果你使用Kramm，你也可以安排这些事情定期发生，所以这就是
And also if you use Krumm you can schedule this stuff to happen on a regular basis as well so that's
这是一件需要牢记的有用的事情。
a useful thing to bear in mind.
现在，这可能需要不同的时间，这取决于我们升级后有多长时间
Now this might take a varying amount of time depending upon how long it's been since since we've upgraded
我们的软件，因为我还没有在这个虚拟机上做过，这将需要相当长的一段时间。
our software and because I haven't actually done it on this virtual machines it will take quite a while.
所以我要做的就是把这里的视频剪下来，完成后再回来。
So I'm going to do is I'm going to cut the video here and come back when it is done.
就像这样变成命令。
And just like that into commands.
我们系统上的所有软件都已升级，我们实际上可以看到Firefox徽标已经
All the software on our system has been upgraded and we can actually see that the Firefox logo has been
更新后看起来更具史诗色彩。
updated to look a whole lot more epic.
请注意，系统也不需要重新启动我们安装的所有软件，即存储库
So notice how the system also didn't need to reboot all the software that we've installed that the repositories
已经升级过了，可以开始使用了。
has been upgraded and it's ready to go.
所以我们所要做的就是使用sudo apt get update更新软件包列表，然后一旦我们更新了它
So all we had to do was update the package list using sudo apt get update and then once we updated it
或者等待升级，然后我们将所有的软件升级到新版本。
or waited it was sudo apt get upgrade and then we upgraded all the software to the new versions.
所以要知道，当您执行这些更新时，有时需要重新启动系统，但这是
So do know that sometimes you will need to reboot your system when you do these updates but this is
这有点不寻常，但有时需要发生。
kind of unusual but sometimes it will need to happen.
但需要注意的是，在执行升级和
But it's important to note that you should always update your cache before you perform an upgrade and
确保使用正确的软件版本进行升级，并且所有内容都统一更新。
make sure that the upgrade occurs using the correct software versions and everything is updated uniformly.
因此，要更新缓存，您已经运行了sudo apt get update，这将会下载
So to update your cache you've run sudo apt get update and what this will do is it will download the
将软件包列表的最新版本从两台服务器保存到您的缓存中，该缓存存储在您的
most updated versions of the package lists from the two servers into your cache that is stored on your
电脑。
computer.
因此，为了做到这一点，你需要有一个互联网连接。
So in order to do that you need to have an internet connection.
但是，一旦您通过下载最新的软件包列表更新了缓存，您就可以升级所有
But once you've updated your cache by downloading the most updated package lists you can upgrade all
使用sudo apt Get Upgrade升级您系统上的软件。
of the software on your system using sudo apt get upgrade.
这样做的目的是让包管理器查看当前使用的所有软件
And what this will do is it will make the package manager look at all the software that is currently
并将其与软件包列表中的可用内容进行比较，然后与软件包管理器中的可用内容进行比较
on your system and compare it to what is available in the package lists and then the package manager
将自动下载和升级所有可下载的不同软件包，以便
will automatically download and upgrade all the different packages that can be downloaded in order to
将您的系统更新到最新级别，以便下载任何新版本的软件包
update your system to the most up to date level so this will download any new versions of packages that
删除旧版本它将下载所有新的所需依赖项。
remove old versions it'll download any new required dependencies.
这只会帮助您了解如何提高您的系统安全性。
And this just helps you know increase your system security.
它帮助您提供最大的功能，它的四周都很棒，但这是您需要的东西
It helps give you maximum functionality and it's all round just fantastic but something that you need
请记住，您需要在升级之前更新缓存，否则您将
to bear in mind is that you need to update the cache before you upgrade because otherwise you'll be
升级所有软件以锁定最新版本，并且您希望能够更新
upgrading all your software to lock the most up to date versions and you want to be able to update your
更新版本的软件要做到这一点，您需要最新的软件包列表，以便更新这些let
software to update versions in order to do that you need uptodate package lists so to update those lets
你更新你的现金，然后当你更新了你的缓存，你就可以操作你的软件了。
you update your cash and then when you've updated your cache you can operate your software.
所以请记住这一点。
So bear that in mind.
在升级软件之前，请始终更新缓存。
Always update your cache before you upgrade your software.
这里要记住的另一件重要事情是，您只能升级已安装的软件
Another important thing to bear in mind here is that you can only upgrade software that was installed
通过储存库。
through the repositories.
好的，这在Gonu Linux系统上是可能的，就像我们在前面的视频中所做的那样，我们在视频中修改了
OK that is possible on a Gonu Linux system like we did in the previous videos where we modified the
ls命令。
ls command.
您可以手动下载包，将其解压并编译，然后自己安装。
You can download packages manually extract them and compile them and install them yourself.
但是因为该过程不是通过存储库和包管理器发生的，所以您失去了
But because that process doesn't happen through the repositories and package manager you lose the ability
让他们保持最新，就像我们在这里做的那样。
to keep them up to date like we are doing here.
因此，如果您可以从网站下载一个包，也可以从缺席者那里获得它
So therefore if you can download a package from a web site and you can also get it from the absentee
存储库确保从存储库获取它，因为这样您就可以确保它符合
repositories make sure to get it from the repositories because then you can make sure that it's up to
日期。
date.
确保您始终拥有可用的最佳功能。
Make sure you always have the best features available.
使用此自动化过程，因此到目前为止，我们已经讨论了如何搜索必须更新缓存的软件
Using this automated process so as of now we've discussed how to search for software had to update caches
以及如何升级软件。
and how to upgrade software.
但我们还没有讨论过必须实际安装新软件。
But we haven't discussed had to actually install new software.
嗯，考虑到你现在的理解，这对你来说真的很容易，所以
Well with all the understanding that you have now that's actually going to be really easy for you so
我会把那颗小宝石留到下一个视频里。
I'll save that little gem for the next video.